I want you to save a fellow magical girl.
Her name is Iroha Tamaki.
All rumors are connected at their core.
Iroha Tamaki went to the Memory Museum and then she disappeared.
The only place she could be is somewhere in the rumor of the Eternal Sakura.
Iroha...Iroha...
It's her doppel!
I'm hungry, Master Yachiyo, you cooked breakfast today!
Don't tell me you forgot, let's go get up!
I'm dying of starvation!
Quit bugging her, let's wash up and wait at the table.
What's going on? The last thing I remember is finding Iroha in that rumor.
Gee, you look super tired today!
Oh, if you're not feeling up to it, me and Iroha can cook.
Iroha?!
Hey, where is Iroha anyway? Still squeaking I bet.
Good morning, Yachiyo. Did I oversleep again?
Are you okay?
I am now.
Yachiyo...
I don't know anyone who can cook a better breakfast than Yachiyo.
Her eggs always look so perfect!
You know, you should get your dad to take some lessons from her.
What for? He's a great cook!
Ban Banzai's food is the best in Kamehama!
I hate to say it, but we've been absorbed by Iroha's topple.
Oh, good! It's right in the middle between awesome and yucky!
I was afraid of that.
What's the deal with this house, though?
Well, I don't mind the food there.
Mikazuki Villa. Those girls and I lived here.
So did Iroha for a bit.
Hey, Kuroe!
If you don't want your ham, can I have it?
I didn't know you and Felicia knew each other.
No, I don't know her. I never met her before.
Oh, hey, Kuroe. That book you let me borrow? It was such a good read.
I get it. You were Iroha's friend.
Yeah, I guess I sorta was.
If you know anything about the labyrinth of this rumor, you need to tell me right now.
It's all written down here.
It's called the Eternal Sakura.
Somehow, its power is tied to Iroha's memories.
Yeah, it looks like it is.
Is something wrong, Yachiyo? You haven't touched your breakfast.
Yroha. It is you, isn't it?
Huh?
If it is you, you're sweet and curious.
And you care about your little sister.
My sister?
My sister!
Wait.
What the heck? Why are we here?
Wow, talk about spacing out.
We're all going to visit my little sister.
I didn't know you had a little sister.
Oh.
Well, she's been in the hospital for a while now.
Here we are!
Uwasa, uwasa, fun and spooky uwasa.
Uwasa, uwasa, weird and kooky uwasa.
We'll make up rumors as homes for the uwasa.
What are the leaders of Magius doing here?
They were friends of Iroha's little sister.
Toka, Nemu and her all shared the same room at the hospital.
That girl in yellow, is she Nemu Hiragi?
That's her.
Hey, your friend's face at the friendship bending staircase.
This one's called the Seance Shrine.
I'm the thing you left behind.
There's good fortune water if what you want's luck.
And endless solitude for lonely moods when your nights are dark.
I wonder how they know about the rumors.
Maybe it's because of Nemu.
She told me she made up all the rumors in Kamehama City.
Are these Iroha's memories all jumbled up?
Or is there a connection between the rumors in Kamehama and this room?
Where's Ui? She should be here.
Who's that?
Iroha's little sister. That's who.
Come on out, Ui, and help us make up some rumors.
That's Ui?
No way.
Yeah, sure.
She wants us all to go to her favorite theme park, to Culation Land.
That would be wonderful!
It'll be okay, Ui. Promise.
When you get better, I'll take you anywhere you want.
I'm your big sis. I'll do whatever I can to make you happy.
I'm here, and I won't leave you ever again.
Where are we? Is it Iroha's imagination? Or are we stuck in her dream?
Is that possible?
It has to be. Everyone Iroha's met are friends here. Like you and the girls at Mikazuki Villa.
And Iroha's the only one who would dream about her missing sister like this.
So this must be her dream.
Stop that!
That proves it. This space isn't real.
You're right. But what could be causing it?
Nemu said she's the one who created the rumors, right?
Yeah.
Everything here is specific to Iroha's experiences, so Nemu couldn't have created it.
The only thing that could have is Iroha's doppel.
They didn't know they could do that?
A soul gem's taint can be confined to a part of your body so you can use its power.
That's a doppel.
And since it's also technically a witch, it can create a labyrinth.
That's true, I guess.
The only way we can escape this dream is by defeating Iroha's doppel.
What worries me is that her doppel's been active too long,
and who knows what kind of damage that's causing to her soul gem.
It could be irreparable.
Find the door.
I don't see one anywhere, do you?
I have a feeling it's in the most obvious place.
This could be an escape route. Or a trap.
Either way, it's the weirdest thing here.
Wait! I'm coming too!
I don't want your help, especially since you're with the Magius.
Go find a place to hide. Stay there until Iroha wakes up.
O-okay.
Um, wait!
If this is Iroha's dream like you say, then is the Iroha in here the real one?
Good question.
I have no proof.
But I think she is all that's real.
So this is her dream, huh?
It's giving me the creeps, just like a witch's labyrinth.
A witch?
There's a witch!
Everyone, be careful!
Kyuubi!
I have left this attack!
Back off, you!
Rada! Maduro!
Yes! We did!
Don't mess with Team Mikazuki Villa!
She looks and sounds enough like the real Iroha.
But how can I tell it's really her?
I have no idea what the point of this dream is. Why would Iroha's doppel want to trap us in it?
I need to figure out how to wake her up.
Good morning, Yachiyo. Did I oversleep?
I think the dream's falling apart.
Come on, wake up! I'm hungry!
Master Yachiyo, you cooked breakfast today!
Don't bug her. Let's wash up and lay at the taste!
Suruno! Let's set off some parachute fireworks!
Those are only fun in the daytime, when we can see them!
There's no point at night!
Kuroi? What's wrong?
Nothing. I was just spacing out a little is all.
You can tell me if something's bothering you.
I don't know how much I can help, but I can certainly try.
Thank you.
Her dream world is calm and peaceful. Just like her.
We should do some of those snake fireworks next!
Those are definitely not fun when it's dark out.
Well, we got some smoke bombs, but that's it for our fireworks.
Save them for tomorrow. Let's have some melon.
If the real person isn't here, she makes a copy of them.
Yachiyo's amazing, isn't she?
She's a magical girl, and she's in college, and she's a model, too!
I saw her on the cover of a magazine yesterday, and I was so proud, I bought a copy for myself!
Remember? When we first met her, she was a little mean, wasn't she?
But that's only because she was worried about us!
Turns out, she's super sweet!
Irohal, are you happy like this?
Huh?
Like, if this were a dream, and you could do anything, what would you want to do the most?
A dream? I never thought about it, but I guess there's nothing else I could hope for.
Huh? Nothing? I'm kind of the same way, I guess.
I'm fine right where I am, doing what I'm doing. I have my friends to share these moments with.
Everyone's shared so much with me already. You, Yachiyo, and the others, too.
Really?
Of all the suspicious things here, you are the most suspicious.
Now then, Ui. Are you Iroha's doppel?
It seems I'm back to square one.
I was wondering, Iroha, why'd you pick a teddy bear?
What do you mean?
Like, why'd you pick that, instead of your real sister?
Why would you say something like that?
It's just, you were looking all over for her, so you obviously care about her.
So it's weird that here...
I mean, she's a teddy bear.
How could you say something so mean?
I was just asking.
Why do you hate her? She never did anything to you.
I don't hate her. I never even met her.
I don't understand.
Why is Ui not human?
Yachiyo, what are you doing way out here?
Iroha, we have to leave this place, now.
But everyone will be sad if you don't come to the hospital.
Where's your sister? Your real sister?
Huh?
Everyone you know is here except Ui.
She's right here, see?
I love my little sis more than anything.
And I'd do pretty much anything if it's for Ui.
No!
Let's go!
Iroha, what's wrong?
Why are you getting in my way?
Iroha? What's wrong?
Iroha Tamaki fell into a deep sleep at the bottom of the room.
But then...
Her fears about her sister and her knowledge about the truth of magical girls caused her to have nightmares.
Disturbing nightmares.
Now, her soul gem has become even more tainted.
Why are you trying to stop me?
I made new dreams to cancel out her nightmares.
I made a new Mikazuki villa.
I worked so hard.
Iroha...
I even made her a new sister.
A new Ui.
A new Ui Tamaki for Iroha Tamaki.
For me.
But when I met you, you were still looking for her.
I couldn't find her.
So I made a new one.
I did it because I'm scared.
I'm scared I'll never see her again.
I'm scared that someday all my friends will disappear too.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
I'll start fresh.
I'll make a new story for Iroha Tamaki.
Leave her alone.
Stop it.
Iroha!
Snap out of it!
This is Iroha Tamaki's new story.
Iroha!
I got you.
I'm sorry.
The doppel was hiding in her the whole time.
It said it created a new sister for Iroha.
With a new Ui and a new Mikazuki villa,
Iroha Tamaki will be happy.
So stop trying to destroy it.
Get back.
It's too dangerous for you here.
Maybe it is.
And I want to save her too!
A new Ui for Iroha.
All her friends are here.
Nothing but happiness.
A better Ui than the real one.
Did you only love your sister because she was cute and fun to play with?
No one can care.
Remember the times you felt sad.
Remember the times you were afraid.
Life wasn't always happy for you.
Mikazuki Villa wasn't a paradise.
Felicia was a brat who picked on you.
And all Sana did was worry about us seeing her.
Stop it.
Remember how you suffered when you found out the fate of magical girls?
Will I remember?
That's when we met.
You must remember that.
Stop it.
You're building a world of lies.
You can't trade our anger, our sorrow for the sake of happiness.
What we felt was real.
Stop it.
Your sister.
Our time at Mikazuki Villa.
Remember them as they are.
Come back, Iroha.
You promised me.
You said you'd never leave.
Yachiyo!
Kuroi, connect!
Right.
Kuroi!
Weplu!
Where are we floating?
Yachiyo!
Kuroi!
Hero!
You're back!
You're back.
You're back. Thank goodness.
I am back. Here to stay.
I'm glad. I'm so glad.
I'm sorry I was gone so long. I promised you I wouldn't die that easy.
I think that promise is the reason I could come back.
Yeah.
I am fine with добав
I am fine with your new
Thank you.